Yaroslav Kolbaiev

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PORTFOLIO

https://portfolio-page-alpha-black.vercel.app/



SUMMARY

I'm a software developer with 2 years experience of building high performance web applications

My passion is coding, self-development and continuous learning of new technologies.

I enjoy working in a team of co-thinkers and sharing my experience with others.

EDUCATION

Master

KHERSON TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY (UKRAINE)

PERSONAL DETAILS

Location

Remote / Relocate

Languages

English (C1)

CONTACTS

+380999139994

yaroslavkolbaiev@gmail.com Telegram

GitHub

LinkedIn: rick-kolbaiev

EXPERIENCE

Student

Mate Academy

Ukraine (Mar 2022 - Dec 2022)

Junior Full Stack Developer

Univislabs

Alanya/Turkey (Jan 2023 - Mar 2024)

Junior Full Stack Developer

Murano Software

Remote (Apr 2024 -Now)

FRONTEND

- JS/TS
- React / Next JS
- Vue / Nuxt
- Vite
- Redux
- Tailwind
- Material UI
- CSS / SASS
- Apollo Client

BACKEND

- Node / Express
- PHP / Laravel
- Python / Django
- Redis
- Selenium
- Apollo GraphQL
- MongoDB/ Mongoose
- PostgreSQL / Maria DB
- Prisma ORM
- Docker / Docker Compose
- Firebase / GCloud
- Socket IO

As a Full Stack Developer, I have extensive experience in building robust and scalable web applications using Laravel and React.js. On the backend, I leverage Laravel's powerful features and Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) principles to design and implement efficient database architectures, write comprehensive tests, and ensure code quality. For the frontend, I utilize React.js, Vite, and Tailwind CSS to create dynamic and responsive user interfaces. My projects are containerized using Docker and orchestrated with Docker Compose, ensuring consistent development and deployment.